<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self">
    <id>https://www.qualityology.com</id>
    <title>Qualityology - Let&#39;s get the most out of life! • Posts by &#34;baby&#34; tag</title>
    <link href="https://www.qualityology.com" />
    <updated>2017-11-13T07:19:14.000Z</updated>
    <category term="tech" />
    <category term="lifestyle" />
    <entry>
        <id>https://www.qualityology.com/lifestyle/best-easiest-way-sterilize-baby-bottles-uv-sterilization/</id>
        <title>Best and easiest way to sterilize baby bottles - UV sterilization</title>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.qualityology.com/lifestyle/best-easiest-way-sterilize-baby-bottles-uv-sterilization/"/>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Baby is vulnerable to diseases and illnesses, so you will want to ensure their bottles are clean and germ free until baby&amp;#x2019;s immune system developed providing a much higher tolerance to bacterias and germs. Sterilizing bottles can have different ways. Some require more efforts and times and some need more cautions. &lt;strong&gt;There are many ways to sterilize baby bottles.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Use&amp;#xA0;electric steamers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Use Microwave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Use boiling water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Use UV sterilizer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Sterilizing Tablets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Many other ways.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best and easiest way to sterilize baby bottles at home is use UV&amp;#xA0;sterilizer if you can get one. &lt;strong&gt;Why use UV sterilizer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; It does not use water, so no worry about germ from steamers water.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; No need to boil. Plastic bottle safe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; UV can kill viruses, germs and bacteria (99.9% rate).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Some sterilizer offer dryer function, save your time for sleep!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only con of this method is usually UV sterilizer is a bit expensive compare to other methods. There are not a lot of options of UV sterilizer in the market. You don&amp;#x2019;t want a products that can only&amp;#xA0;sterilize one bottle or one nipple at a time because you will have more than one bottle need to be sterilized. If you don&amp;#x2019;t know which one to get, you can consider the&amp;#xA0;Wabi Baby Touch Panel Dual Function UV Sterilizer &amp;amp; Dryer. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is available at Amazon and Wabi&amp;#x2019;s website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Get-one-from-Amazon-Wabi-Baby-Touch-Panel-Dual-Function-UV-Sterilizer-amp-Dryer&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Get-one-from-Amazon-Wabi-Baby-Touch-Panel-Dual-Function-UV-Sterilizer-amp-Dryer&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Get one from Amazon: Wabi Baby Touch Panel Dual Function UV Sterilizer &amp;amp; Dryer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Get one from Amazon: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07195QKZC/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B07195QKZC&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=all4oscom-20&amp;amp;linkId=46bd14015f4146986852b0978ac71e30&#34;&gt;Wabi Baby Touch Panel Dual Function UV Sterilizer &amp;amp; Dryer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wabi Baby Touch Panel Dual Function UV Sterilizer &amp;amp; Dryer have sterilizer and dryer function so all you need to do is wash the bottles and put them into Wabi UV sterilizer &amp;amp; dryer. We tested one&amp;#xA0;Wabi Baby Touch Panel Dual Function UV Sterilizer &amp;amp; Dryer and found it is a nice product for family with new baby. Wabi UV sterilizer &amp;amp; dryer is not the small one you usually see in the market. The box width is about the mid size computer case. But it is lighter than it looks like. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/2017/11/wabi-uv-sterilizer-dryer.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wabi Uv Sterilizer Dryer&#34;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will find this UV sterilizer looks very well made and nice. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/2017/11/wabi-uv-sterilizer-dryer-unbox.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wabi Uv Sterilizer Dryer Unbox&#34;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has touch panel for function control. Very simple and easy to use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/2017/11/wabi-uv-sterilizer-dryer-touch-functions.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wabi Uv Sterilizer Dryer Touch Functions&#34;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not too small, but not too big. We use 8oz bottle in our test.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/2017/11/wabi-uv-sterilizer-dryer-size.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wabi Uv Sterilizer Dryer Size&#34;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looks very cool also when it is on. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/2017/11/wabi-uv-sterilizer-dryer-on.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wabi Uv Sterilizer Dryer On&#34;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We tested the UV and dryer function for a set of bottles. After the full cycle complete, all bottles were dry and feels clean. It does left some warm feeling when finish, but that is totally normal.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        <category term="lifestyle" />
        <updated>2017-11-13T07:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>Qualityology</author>
    </entry>
</feed>