<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://www.qualityology.com</id>
    <title>Qualityology - Let&#39;s get the most out of life! • Posts by &#34;wireless&#34; tag</title>
    <link href="https://www.qualityology.com" />
    <updated>2017-10-26T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
    <category term="tech" />
    <category term="lifestyle" />
    <entry>
        <id>https://www.qualityology.com/lifestyle/get-free-25-cricket-wireless-credit-new-customer/</id>
        <title>Get Free $25 Cricket Wireless Credit for New Customer - Expired</title>
        <link rel="alternate" href="https://www.qualityology.com/lifestyle/get-free-25-cricket-wireless-credit-new-customer/"/>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Why use Cricket Wireless?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Cricket Wireless uses AT&amp;amp;T cell towers so it will have native AT&amp;amp;T coverage plus some domestic roaming.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  You can even have Canada and Mexico roaming coverage when traveling by paying $10 more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Cricket Wireless get new feature even faster than AT&amp;amp;T&amp;#x2019;s prepaid plan (former AT&amp;amp;T gophone). For example, Cricket Wireless user have VoLTE (Voice over LTE) now while AT&amp;amp;T&amp;#x2019;s prepaid plan still missing that option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Tax is included. Why pay 20% more tax?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Affordable family plan, 5 lines for $100! No hidden fee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Local stores everywhere if you need assistence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;  Cricket Wireless offer more GB than other competitors in same price.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only downside is Cricket Wireless limit the max LTE peak download speeds to 8 Mbps, however, that is fast enough to watch HD video. If you&amp;#x2019;re a new customer looking to try Cricket Wireless and want to save even more, you can use our&amp;#xA0; referral for a $25 Credit for each line. If you&amp;#x2019;re planning on moving multiple lines, after you activate your own line, then refer your other lines so you receive your own $25 credit for each line! After you have them all transferred, you should be able to group them all together for some major group discounts by calling customer service. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;***&lt;strong&gt;Cricket no longer offer referral credit now&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to claim the $25 credit?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Open the referral link: Cricket Rewards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Set up your Cricket Rewards account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Activate Cricket service within 30 days of the referral and update your phone number within the Cricket Rewards app if you got a new one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Keep your account active and in good standing for 60 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can refer your friend using the Cricket Rewards account too. Both parties will receive $25 Credit.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        <category term="lifestyle" />
        <updated>2017-10-26T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
    </entry>
</feed>